[Subtitles by danielsangeo]
Mm...that was good.
Now I need to find a sink.
My hands have cheese powder on them.
I can't just wipe them off on somebody
else's labcoat like I normally do.
Well, I could use the dead guy's
labcoat, but that's not sanitary.
Feeling up dead people
is how you get germs.
Where am I going?
I guess I'll check out that office.
Oh!  Is that a shotgun?
Who keeps a shotgun
and extra ammo in their office?
That's hardcore.
Who's the sheriff now?
YEAH!
I could do this all day.
I need to find some more stuff to shoot.
Shooting the bodies would look cool, but
I don't want to get that stuff on me.
Oh, what about that locked door?
I'll make a new door with this baby.
Call me Ali Baba!
Open sesame!
Fine then!  Close sesame!
Man, three rounds of
buckshot point blank.
What the hell?
It's like one of those
doors from Looney Tunes
where they blow up the whole
building but the door's still standing.
I bet it's locked on both sides
and nobody has the key.
Let's see, can I climb up this?
I don't think I can.
Those edges are slanted.
So, even if I could reach it,
I'd just slide right off.
You'd think they don't want people
climbing the elevator shaft.
Well, there's a ladder.
I could-- I can jump that.
I'm going to need a
running start, though.
This right here is why you
should eat Wheaties in the morning.
I guess any breakfast is better for you
than the two shots of vodka I had.
Whatever, let's do this.
Hoogasaka hoogasaka hoo!
Oh shit, oh shit, oh shi--!
HEV activated.
Automatic medical systems engaged.
Major fracture detected.
Internal bleeding detected.
Emergency: User death imminent.